

Siom Maurya

Date of birth: 10/07/1997 | Nationality: Indian | Gender: Male | Phone

number: (+91) 8452072791 (Mobile) | Email address: siommaurya26@gmail.com |

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/siom-maurya-a20982124/

Address: 400081, mumbai, India (Home)

About me:

I have 4 year experience in MNC. I am fluent in English. I am percieved as an energetic, committed and fast learner. I am looking for job as data engineer where I can use my skill and experience to implement the company's policies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

22/08/2022 - CURRENT Banglore, India

SYSTEM ENGINEER INFOSYS LIMITED

Automated software deployment and configuration management with agile

Experience in CI/CD pipelines like AWS code pipeline, code commit and Jenkins.

Worked on ETL project by using AWS glue, Athena, redshift and lambda.

Hands on experience on implementing cloud solutions using various AWS services and databases.

Good knowledge of microservices and REST API.

Webhosting services installation on EC2 instances.

Development of VPC, route table, private and public subnet.

Research, configured and monitor security software with agile methodology.

18/07/2019 - 30/07/2022 Mumbai, India

CONSULTANT TATA CONSULTANT ENGINEERS LIMITED

Coordination with internal and external stakeholders in order to collect and document technical requirement.

Discussing priorities simultaneously and drive projects to completion with Project managers.

Data analysis on multiple databases by using SQL and python.

Discuss ideas with project manager & ensure that required standards and processes are in place.

Ensure to follow up on innovative solutions and improve process efficiency.

Perform data analysis from data collected from different sources.

Ensure to follow up thing on different engineering files and formats, identifying their patterns in straight forward manner.

Hands on experience on Linux system to manage user data server.

01/11/2017 - 01/01/2018 Mumbai, India

INTERN POLFROST AIRCON PVT LTD

Making mini software in Microsoft visual basic for estimation of cooling capacity of cold room Reviewed and documented system infrastructure and developed improvement strategies. Optimize system operations and improve performance where possible.

Worked on others client software to understand the design model and configuration of software.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

05/05/2015 - 05/05/2019

BACHELOR OF MECHANICAL ENGINEERING University of Mumbai - Lokmanya tilak college of Engineering

Address Navi Mumbai, Mumbai | Final grade 8.71/10

Link https://drive.google.com/file/d/1tl-tUHtWvTBAtYNwpBF8pmfHMZ-5NEAz/view?usp=share_link

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **ENGLISH- PROFICIENT**

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

CERTIFICATIONS

Technical Certification

AWS Solution Architect, Devops Professional, Data engineering AWS cloud, CI/CD pipelines using jenkins, Infosys Project Execution Process

SKILL

Technical Skills

Python, SQL, AWS cloud computing, jenkins, Linux, docker, AWS S3, Redshift, Lambda, data warehouse, relational database, ETL tool, JMeter, Performance testing,

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Social activity, Social Networking, Watching movies, Playing guitar